这里是 LeadFlow Memory 的转化 Agent 工作台。
This is the LeadFlow Memory conversion agent workbench.
选中高意向线索陈薇，调出她的完整客户画像。
Select high-intent lead Chen Wei and open her full profile.
预算、区域、需求和来源信号都来自长期记忆。
Budget, district, needs and source signals all come from long-term memory.
跟进话术由记忆驱动，并标注了本次用到的记忆。
The follow-up script is memory-driven and cites the memory it used.
MemWal 记忆页展示沉淀下来的长期语义记忆。
The MemWal tab shows the accumulated long-term semantic memory.
Walrus 物料页里每一份材料都可被验证。
On the Walrus tab, every artifact is verifiable.
Agent Trace 完整记录了智能体的决策轨迹。
Agent Trace records the full decision trail of the agent.
底部时间线串起从发现到跟进的每一步进度。
The bottom timeline links every step from discovery to follow-up.
界面支持中英文一键切换。
The interface switches between Chinese and English in one click.
记忆让每一次跟进都更懂客户。
Memory makes every follow-up understand the customer better.